Guide to the Norman E. Thomas Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Documentation Files by Subject, Series V
  - BU-BX Church
    - BX 4.2 World Confessionalism: Faith and Order Conversations (Box 26, Folder 227)
    - BX 4.5 Roman Catholic-Protestant Cooperation (Box 26, Folder 228)
    - BX 5.0 World Council of Churches (WCC) (Box 26, Folder 229)
    - BX 7.8 NCCUSA (Box 26, Folder 230)
    - BX 7.9 Consultation on Church Union (COCU) (Box 27, Folder 231)
    - BX 8 Local and State Ecumenism (Ohio) (Box 27, Folder 232)
    - BX 1000 Roman Catholicism (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - BX 4800 Protestantism: General (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - BX 7600 Society of Friends (Box 27, Folder 235)
    - Unification Church (Box 27, Folder 236)
  - BY Methodism
    - BY 22 Methodism: General Works (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - BY 25 World Methodist Council (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - BY 100 Polity and Worship (Box 27, Folder 240)
    - BY 250 History: General (Box 27, Folder 241)
    - BY 400 The Wesleys (Box 27, Folder 242)
    - Methodism: Theology (Box 27, Folder 243)
    - BY 1000 Methodism: Europe (Box 27, Folder 244)
    - BY1500 Methodism: USA (Box 28, Folder 245)
    - BY 6000 Methodism: Latin America (Box 28, Folder 246)
    - BY 6500 Methodism: Asia (Box 28, Folder 247)
    - BY 7000 Methodism: Oceania (Box 28, Folder 248)
    - BY 7600 Methodism: Africa (Box 28, Folder 249)
    - BY 8255 Methodism: Zimbabwe (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - D History
    - DT Africa: General (Box 28, Folder 251)
    - DT 950.5 Zimbabwe: Shona History (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - E American History
    - E American History (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - F Economics
    - FA Economics: General Works (Box 29, Folder 254)
    - FB 2 Socialism; Marxism (Box 29, Folder 255)
    - FC Economic Development (Box 29, Folder 256)
    - FC 5 Economic Development: Africa (Box 29, Folder 257)
    - Zimbabwe (Box 29, Folder 258)
    - FD 5 Land Policies: Ecology (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - FE 1 Industry; Management (Box 30, Folder 260)
    - FG Commerce (Coops; Credit Unions) (Box 30, Folder 261)
    - FH 1 International Finance (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - GA Geography: Maps
    - Maps (Box 30, Folder 263)
  - GN Anthropology
    - GN 1 General: Theory (Box 30, Folder 264)
    - GN 3.4 Shona Culture (Zimbabwe) (Box 30, Folder 265)
    - GN 4 Traditional Religion (Box 30, Folder 266)
    - GN 4.5 Shona Religion (Zimbabwe) (Box 30, Folder 267)
  - H Sociology
    - H 0 Sociology: General (Box 30, Folder 268)
    - HA 1 Research Methods (Box 30, Folder 269)
    - HA 4.1 Social Surveys: Africa (Box 31, Folder 270)
    - HQ Family; Marriage (Box 31, Folder 271)
    - HQ1 Family and Marriage: Africa (CROMIA Project) (Box 31, Folder 272)
    - HQ2 Women's Rights (Box 31, Folder 273)
    - HR Population; Migration (Box 31, Folder 274)
    - HR1 Refugees (Box 31, Folder 275)
    - HS2 Mass Media (Box 31, Folder 276)
    - HT Urban Sociology: General (Box 32, Folder 277)
    - HT1.5 Urbanization: Africa (Box 32, Folder 278)
    - HW1 Race Relations: General (Box 32, Folder 279)
    - HW7 Race Relations: USA (Box 32, Folder 280)
    - HW9 Race Relations: South Africa (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - I Psychology
    - IF Personality (Box 32, Folder 282)
    - IG Personality: Africa (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - J Political Science
    - Political Science (Box 32, Folder 284)
    - Marxism: General (Box 32, Folder 285)
    - JK USA (Box 33, Folder 286)
    - JK5 Puerto Rico (Box 33, Folder 287)
    - JL6 Caribbean (Box 33, Folder 289)
    - JL7 Cuba (Box 33, Folder 290)
    - JL 14 Central America (Box 33, Folder 291)
    - JL 15 El Salvador (Box 33, Folder 292)
    - JL 16 Nicaragua (Box 33, Folder 293)
    - JL 17 Panama (Box 33, Folder 294)
    - JL21 Argentina (Box 33, Folder 296)
    - JL23 Bolivia (Box 33, Folder 297)
    - JL26 Chile (Box 33, Folder 298)
    - JN Europe (Box 33, Folder 299)
    - JN65 USSR (Box 33, Folder 300)
    - India (Box 34, Folder 301)
    - JQ2 Asia: General (Box 34, Folder 302)
    - JQ8 Vietnam., Cambodia, Loas (Box 34, Folder 303)
    - JQ15China (Box 34, Folder 304)
    - JQ18 Middle East (Box 34, Folder 305)
    - JQ18.5 Israel/Palestine (Box 34, Folder 306)
    - JQ19 Africa: General (Box 34, Folder 307)
    - JQ21 International Defense and Aid Fund (Box 34, Folder 308)
    - JQ25 Southern Africa (Box 34, Folder 309)
    - JQ25.2 Angola (Box 35, Folder 310)
    - JQ25.5 Mozambique (Box 35, Folder 311)
    - JQ25.7 Namibia (Box 35, Folder 312)
    - JQ27 South Africa: Political (Box 35, Folder 313)
    - JQ27.5 South Africa: Economic and Social (apartheid) (Box 35, Folder 314)
    - JQ28 Southern Rhodesia: Political History to 1980 (Box 35, Folder 315)
    - JQ28.5 Zimbabwe: Political History (1980- (Box 35, Folder 316)
    - JQ29 East Africa (Box 35, Folder 317)
    - JQ30 West Africa (Box 35, Folder 318)
    - JQ36 Central Africa (Zaire) (Box 36, Folder 319)
    - JQ38 North Africa (Box 36, Folder 320)
    - JX13 International Relations (Box 36, Folder 321)
    - JX20 United Nations (Box 36, Folder 322)
  - K Law
    - General (Box 36, Folder 323)
  - L Education
    - L General (Box 36, Folder 324)
    - LA Theory; Methods (Box 36, Folder 325)
    - LC53 Adult Education (Non Formal Education: newsletter) (Box 36, Folder 326)
    - LC60 Education for Development (Box 36, Folder 327)
    - LG400 Africa (Box 36, Folder 328)
    - LG461 Zimbabwe [Rhodesia] (Box 37, Folder 329)
  - M Mission and Evangelism
    - MA1.0 Bibliography (Box 37, Folder 330)
    - MA1.3 Documentation and Archives (Box 37, Folder 331)
    - MA2.0 General Works (Box 37, Folder 332)
    - MA4.0 Study and Teaching (Box 37, Folder 333)
    - MA4.1 Syllabi and Bibliographies (Box 37, Folder 334)
    - MA4.2 Case Studies (Box 37, Folder 335)
    - MB1.5 Theology of Mission: General (Box 37, Folder 336)
    - MB2.0 Bible and Missions (Box 38, Folder 337)
    - MC2.0 Mission: Ecumenical Aspects (Box 38, Folder 338)
    - MC3.0 History: General (Box 38, Folder 339)
    - MD3.0 History: Early and Medieval (Box 38, Folder 341)
    - MD4.0 History: Modern (Box 38, Folder 342)
    - MD6.0 Roman Catholic (Box 38, Folder 344)
    - MD7.0 Protestant Mission Societies (Box 38, Folder 345)
    - MD7.M Methodist Mission Societies (Box 38, Folder 346)
  - ME Evangelism
    - ME1.5 Teaching: Syllabi (Box 38, Folder 347)
    - ME1.6 Teaching: Case Studies (Box 39, Folder 348)
    - ME2.0 Evangelism: General (Box 39, Folder 349)
    - Letter on Evangelism (Box 39, Folder 350)
    - ME2.5 Theology (Box 39, Folder 351)
    - ME3.1 History: 18th Century (the Wesleys) (Box 39, Folder 353)
    - ME3.2 History 19th Century (Box 39, Folder 354)
    - ME3.4 History 20th Century Roman Catholic (Box 39, Folder 355)
    - ME3.6 History: 20th Century Evangelical Protestant (Box 39, Folder 356)
    - ME3.7 History: 20th Century: United Methodist (Box 39, Folder 357)
    - ME3.8 History: 20th Century: Two-thirds World (Box 39, Folder 358)
    - ME4.0 Church Growth: General (Box 40, Folder 359)
    - ME4.01 Theology and Bible (Box 40, Folder 360)
    - ME4.02 Principles (Box 40, Folder 361)
    - ME4.03 Membership Trends (Box 40, Folder 362)
    - ME4.04 The Unchurched (Box 40, Folder 363)
    - ME4.05 Global and Case Studies (Box 40, Folder 364)
    - ME4.1 Evangelism: Methods: General (Box 40, Folder 365)
    - ME4.12Methods: United Methodist Churches (Box 41, Folder 367)
    - ME4.13 Methods: Other Denominations (Box 41, Folder 368)
    - ME4.2 Church Planting (Box 41, Folder 369)
    - ME4.25 New Congragational Development (UMC newsletter) (Box 41, Folder 370)
    - Forward -UMC (Box 41, Folder 371)
    - ME5.0 Pastoral Evangelism: General (Box 41, Folder 372)
    - ME5.1 Community Surveys/Census (Box 41, Folder 373)
    - ME5.2 Congregational Analysis (Box 41, Folder 374)
    - ME5.30 Evangelism Planning: Judicatory (Box 41, Folder 375)
    - ME5.35 Evangelism Planning:Local Church (Box 41, Folder 376)
    - ME5.4 Evangelism Case Studies: Local (Box 41, Folder 377)
    - ME5.5 Evangelism: Small Church; town and Country (Box 42, Folder 378)
    - ME5.6 Urban Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 379)
    - ME5.7 The Pastor as Evangelist (Box 42, Folder 380)
    - ME5.8 Worship and Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 381)
    - Revival (Box 42, Folder 382)
    - ME5.9 Christian Education and Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 383)
    - ME6.1 Psychology of Evangelism and Conversion (Box 42, Folder 385)
    - ME6.2 Spiritual Gifts (Box 42, Folder 386)
    - ME6.3 Witnessing; Faith Sharing (Box 42, Folder 387)
    - ME6.4 Training for Personal Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 388)
    - ME6.6 Small Group Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 389)
    - Assimilation (Box 42, Folder 390)
    - ME7.0 Prophetic Evangelism (Box 42, Folder 391)
    - ME7.1 Crusade Evangelism (Box 43, Folder 392)
    - ME7.2 The Media and Evangelism (Box 43, Folder 393)
    - MG2.0 Missions: Methods: General (Box 43, Folder 394)
    - MG3.1 Mission/Church Relations: Moratorium (Box 43, Folder 395)
    - Mission/Church Relations: UMC (Box 43, Folder 396)
    - MG4.0 Mission Administration, Planning and Evaluation (Box 43, Folder 397)
    - MG6.0 Education for Mission: General (Box 43, Folder 398)
    - MG6.1 Mission Study: Adults (Box 43, Folder 399)
    - MG7.0 Mission Finance (Box 43, Folder 400)
    - MG8.1 Future of Missions (Box 44, Folder 401)
    - MG9.0 Third World Missions (Box 44, Folder 402)
    - MH2.0 Missions: Social Aspects: General (Box 44, Folder 403)
    - MH3.2 Gospel and Culture (Box 44, Folder 404)
    - MH3.3 The Gospel and Our Culture (newsletter) (Box 44, Folder 405)
    - MH3.5 Unreached Peoples; Frontier Missions (Box 44, Folder 406)
    - MJ Missions and Political Life (Box 44, Folder 407)
    - MM2.0 Missionaries: General (Box 45, Folder 408)
    - MM3.0 Types of Missionaries (Box 45, Folder 409)
    - Mission: Personnel Options (Box 45, Folder 410)
    - MM4.0 Recruitment and Training (Box 45, Folder 411)
    - MP Communications and Missions (Box 45, Folder 412)
    - MP6.0 Media and Missions (Box 45, Folder 413)
    - MS Spirituality, Worship and Mission (Box 45, Folder 414)
    - MT1.5 Missions: Africa: General (Box 45, Folder 415)
    - MT2.0 Missions: Central Africa (Box 45, Folder 416)
    - MT3.0 Missions: Eastern Africa (Box 45, Folder 417)
    - MT5.0 Missions: Southern Africa (Box 45, Folder 418)
    - MT5.S2 Missions: South Africa (Box 46, Folder 419)
    - MT5.Z2 Missions: Zimbabwe (Box 46, Folder 420)
    - MT6.0 Missions: West Africa (Box 46, Folder 421)
    - MU1.5 Missions: Latin America: General (Box 46, Folder 422)
    - MU7.0 Missions: USA (Box 46, Folder 423)
    - MV1.5 Missions: Asia: General (Box 46, Folder 424)
    - MV2.0 Missions: East Asia: General (Box 46, Folder 425)
    - MV2.C2 Missions: China (Box 46, Folder 426)
    - MV2.J2 Missions: Japan (Box 46, Folder 427)
    - MV2.K1 Missions: Korea (Box 46, Folder 428)
    - MV4.0 Missions: South Asia (Box 46, Folder 429)
    - MV5.0 Missions: Southeast Asia (Box 46, Folder 430)
    - MW Missions: Europe (Box 46, Folder 431)
    - Missions: Oceania (Box 46, Folder 432)
  - R Medicine
    - RA3 Church and Health Issues (Box 46, Folder 433)
    - RA3.5 Church and Health for All by 2000 (Box 46, Folder 434)
  - S Agriculture
    - S1 Agriculture: General (Box 46, Folder 435)
    - S2 Agriculture: Zimbabwe (Box 47, Folder 436)
  - U Sociology of Religion
    - UA Sociology of Religion: General (Box 47, Folder 437)
    - UA1 Sociology of Religion: Teaching (Box 47, Folder 438)
    - UA2 Religious Surveys (USA; Phillipines) (Box 47, Folder 439)
    - UA3 Religious Surveys: Africa (Box 47, Folder 440)
    - UB1 Religion and African Culture (Box 47, Folder 441)
    - UB2 Religion and American Culture (Box 47, Folder 442)
    - UB3 Morals and Religion (Box 48, Folder 443)
    - UB4 Religion and Human Stress (Box 48, Folder 444)
    - UC Types of Religious Organizations: General (Box 48, Folder 445)
    - UC1.1 Hare Krishna (Box 48, Folder 446)
    - UC1.2 New Age Movements (Box 48, Folder 447)
    - UC3 African Initiated Churches (AICs) (Box 48, Folder 448)
    - UC3.5 Zimbabwe AICs (Box 49, Folder 449)
    - UD Religious Leadership (Box 49, Folder 450)
    - UE Religion and Social Status (Box 49, Folder 451)
    - UF Women and Religion (Box 49, Folder 452)
    - UG Religion and Social Change (Box 49, Folder 453)
    - Religion and Urban Society (Box 49, Folder 454)
  - V Christian Ethics
    - VA0.1 Christian Ethics: Bibliography (Box 49, Folder 455)
    - VA0.2 Christian Ethics: Teaching (Box 49, Folder 456)
    - VA1 Social Ethics: General (Box 49, Folder 457)
    - VA2 Strategies for Social Action (Box 50, Folder 458)
    - VB1 Biblical Ethics (Box 50, Folder 459)
    - VB2 Theological Ethics (Box 50, Folder 460)
    - VD Principles of Christian Ethics: General (Box 50, Folder 461)
    - VD1 Principles: World Council of Churches (Box 50, Folder 462)
    - VD2 Principles: United Methodist Church (Box 50, Folder 463)
    - VE1 Sexual ethics: General (Box 50, Folder 464)
    - VE1.8 Sexual Orientation: Homosexuality (Box 50, Folder 465)
    - VE3 Types of Marriage: General (Box 50, Folder 466)
    - VE6.1 Population; Family Planning; Abortion (Box 50, Folder 467)
    - VE7 Divorce (Box 50, Folder 468)
    - VG5 Race Relations: General (Box 50, Folder 469)
    - VG5.5 Task of the Church (Box 50, Folder 470)
    - VG5.6 Programme to Combat Racism (WCC) (Box 51, Folder 471)
    - VG5.7 USA (Box 51, Folder 472)
    - VG5.8 Africa (Box 51, Folder 473)
    - VG5.9 Southern Africa (Box 51, Folder 474)
    - VG5.95 South Africa (Box 51, Folder 475)
    - VG5.96 Zimbabwe (Box 52, Folder 476)
    - VG7.5 Ethnic Relations: India (Box 52, Folder 477)
    - Ethics: Economic (Box 52, Folder 478)
    - VK0 Development Ethic (Box 52, Folder 479)
    - VK0.5 Development Ethic: Education Programs (Box 52, Folder 480)
    - VK1 Hunger; Poverty (Box 53, Folder 481)
    - VK1.1 Bread for the World (Box 53, Folder 482)
    - VK1.2 Hunger: Church Responses (Box 53, Folder 483)
    - VK2.5 Science and Technology (Box 53, Folder 484)
    - VK2.55 Faith, Science, and the Future (Box 53, Folder 485)
    - VK2.6 Ecology (Box 54, Folder 486)
    - VK2.7 Land and Water Use (Box 54, Folder 487)
    - VK2.8 Energy Ethics (Box 54, Folder 488)
    - VK4 Labor: Work: Vocation (Box 54, Folder 489)
    - VK5 Lifestyle (Box 54, Folder 490)
    - VK7 Role of Government; Public Finance; Taxation (Box 54, Folder 491)
    - VK8.1 Interfaith Committee on Corporate Responsibity (Box 54, Folder 492)
    - VK8.2 Nestle Boycott (Box 54, Folder 493)
    - International Economy: Multinationals (Box 54, Folder 494)
    - VK8.3 Multinational Corporations and Southern Africa (Box 55, Folder 495)
    - VK8.4 Multinational Corporations and South Africa (Box 55, Folder 496)
    - VK9 Church and Economic Life (Box 55, Folder 497)
    - VK9.5 Church and Economic Life: Africa (Box 56, Folder 498)
    - VL Leisure: Recreation (Box 56, Folder 499)
    - VL1 Tourism (Box 56, Folder 500)
    - VL5 Alcohol and Drugs (Box 56, Folder 501)
    - VM Medical Ethics (Box 56, Folder 502)
    - VM! Bioethics (Box 56, Folder 503)
    - VP1 Political Ethics: General (Box 56, Folder 504)
    - VP1.5 Nationalism (Box 56, Folder 505)
    - VP2.3 Christianity and Marxism (Box 56, Folder 506)
    - VP2.4 Christianity and Communism (Box 56, Folder 507)
    - VP2.5 Christianity and Democracy (Box 56, Folder 508)
    - VP2.8 Christianity and Liberation (Box 57, Folder 509)
    - VP3 Human Rights (Box 57, Folder 510)
    - VP3.5 Refugees; Sanctuary (Box 57, Folder 511)
    - VP6 Christians, Churches and Politics: General (Box 57, Folder 513)
    - VP8 Church and State: General (Box 57, Folder 514)
    - VP8.335 Church and State: China (Box 57, Folder 515)
    - VP8.338 Church and State: The Phillipines (Box 57, Folder 516)
    - VP8.340 Washington Notes on Africa (newsletter) (Box 58, Folder 517)
    - Church and State: Africa: General (Box 58, Folder 518)
    - VP8.343 Church and State: East Africa (Box 58, Folder 519)
    - Church and State: USA (Box 58, Folder 520)
    - VP8.343.6 Church and State: Tanzania (Box 58, Folder 521)
    - VP8.343.7 Church and State: Uganda (Box 58, Folder 522)
    - VP8.343.9 Church and State: Zambia (Box 58, Folder 523)
    - VP8.344 Church and State: Southern Africa (Box 58, Folder 524)
    - VP8.344.1 The Church and Southern Africa (NCCUSA Consultation, 1977) (Box 58, Folder 525)
    - VP8.344.2 Church and State: Angola (Box 59, Folder 526)
    - VP8.344.4 Church and State: Mozambique (Box 59, Folder 527)
    - VP8.344.6 Church and State: Namibia (Box 59, Folder 528)
    - VP8.345 Church and State: South Africa (Box 59, Folder 529)
    - VP8.346 Church and State: Zimbabwe (Box 59, Folder 530)
    - VP8.348 Church and State: Europe (Box 60, Folder 532)
    - Church and State: Latin America (Box 60, Folder 533)
    - Church and State: Asia (Box 60, Folder 534)
    - VW3, VW3.5 Peace;War (Box 60, Folder 535)
    - VW$ World Order (Box 61, Folder 537)
- Documentation Files by Institution/Organization, Series VI
  - Lausanne Committee for World Evangelization (LCWE)
    - Conference: Delegates, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 538)
    - Conference: News Releases (Box 61, Folder 539)
    - Conference: Papers (Box 61, Folder 540)
    - Conference: Reports (Box 61, Folder 541)
    - Conference: Interpretative Writings (Box 61, Folder 542)
  - Mission Society for United Methodists
    - Mission Society for United Methodists: Papers (Box 62, Folder 543)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ)
    - NCCJ: Papers (Box 62, Folder 544)
  - Oxford Institute of Methodist Theological Studies
    - Oxford Institute of Methodist Theological Studies: Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 545)
  - Parliament of the World's Religions
    - Parliament of the World's Religions: General information;newsletters (Box 62, Folder 546)
    - Parliament: Papers of Participating Groups, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 547)
  - Partnership in Mission (PIM)
    - Partnership in Mission: Papers, 1981-1986 (Box 62, Folder 548)
  - United Methodist Church, Board of Global Ministries
    - General (Box 62, Folder 549)
    - Handbooks (Box 62, Folder 550)
    - Reports (Box 63, Folder 551)
    - Promotional Material (Box 63, Folder 552)
    - Consultations: Staff with UMC Mission Professors, 1980-2001 (Box 63, Folder 553)
    - Global Gathering: Papers, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 554)
    - Health for All Team Visit to Latin America, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 555)
    - Assembly: Papers, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 556)
    - Assembly: Delegates' Materials, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 557)
    - Harare: Documents: General/Plenary (Box 64, Folder 558)
    - Harare: Interpretative Writings (Box 64, Folder 559)
    - Harare: Miscellaneous Papers (Box 64, Folder 560)
    - Harare: Newspaper (Jubilee), daily (Box 64, Folder 561)
    - Harare: Plenary Addresses (Box 64, Folder 562)
    - Harare: Press Releases (Box 64, Folder 563)
    - Harare: Profles of Key Participants (Box 64, Folder 564)
    - Harare: Public Issues including Human Rights (Box 64, Folder 565)
    - Harare: Women's Pre-Assenbly Festival (Box 64, Folder 566)
    - Harare: Worship Resources (Box 64, Folder 567)
    - World Mission Conference: Delegates' Materials, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 568)
    - Melbourne: Documents: General/Plenary (Box 65, Folder 569)
    - Melbourne: Documents: Sections (Box 65, Folder 570)
    - Melbourne: Interpretative Writings (Box 65, Folder 571)
    - Melbourne: Miscellaneous Papers (Box 65, Folder 572)
    - Melbourne: Preparatory Papers (Box 65, Folder 573)
    - Melbourne: Profiles of Key Participants (Box 65, Folder 574)
    - Melbourne: Worship Materials (Box 65, Folder 575)
    - World Mission Conference: Delegates' Materials, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 576)
    - San Antonio: Encuentro Documents (Box 66, Folder 577)
    - UMC Supervising Pastor (Box 66, Folder 578)
    - San Antonio: Interpretative Writings (Box 66, Folder 579)
    - San Antonio: Press Releases (Box 66, Folder 580)
    - San Antonio: Worship Resources (Box 66, Folder 581)
    - World Mission Conference: Delegates Materials, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 582)
    - Salvador: Documents (Box 66, Folder 583)
    - Salvador: Miscellaneous Papers (Box 66, Folder 584)
    - Salvador: Press Releases (Box 66, Folder 585)
    - Salvador: Worship Resources (Box 66, Folder 586)
  - World Evangelical Fellowship (WEF)
    - WEF: Directory: Global Report, 1985-1989 (Box 67, Folder 587)
  - Yale-Edinburgh Conference
    - Yale-Edinburgh Conference: Papers, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 588)
  - World Missionary Conference 1910 Centennial celebrations
    - Edinburgh 2010: Conference handbook, program documentation, papers from conference in Edinburgh, 2010 Jun 2-6 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - 2010 Boston: Conference program, "Tracing Contours: Reflections on World Mission and Christianity"; conference papers, 2010 Nov 4-7 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Biographical Documentation, Series VII
  - General
    - CVs and biographical reports (Box 67, Folder 589)
    - List of published writings and public lectures, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Publications about NET
    - Publications about Norman E. Thomas (Box 67, Folder 590)
  - Ecclesiastical and Academic Appointments
    - Africa Task Force: Planning (Box 67, Folder 591)
    - Africa Task Force: Background Papers (Box 67, Folder 592)
    - Africa Task Force: Documents for Task Force Members (Box 67, Folder 593)
    - Field Notes: ATF Africa trip, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 594)
    - Africa Task Force: Reports (Box 67, Folder 595)
    - Africa Task Force: Follow-up and Interpretation (Box 67, Folder 596)
    - Africa Church Growth and Development Committee (Box 68, Folder 597)
    - BUST: course offerings (Box 68, Folder 599)
    - BUST: Reports and Evaluations (Box 68, Folder 600)
    - BUST: Doctor of Ministry Program (Box 68, Folder 601)
    - Ordained Elder, New Hampshire Annual Conference, The United Methodist Church, 1978-1983 (Box 68, Folder 602)
    - Ordained Elder, West Ohio Annual Conference, the United Methodist Church, 1983- (Box 68, Folder 603)
    - UTS: Advisees (Box 68, Folder 604)
    - UTS: Core Groups (Box 68, Folder 605)
    - UTS: Course Offerings (Box 68, Folder 606)
    - UTS: D. Miss. Program (Box 68, Folder 607)
    - UTS: Evaluations (Box 68, Folder 608)
    - UTS: Long-range Planning (Box 68, Folder 609)
    - Publicity/photos (Box 69, Folder 610)
    - UTS contracts (Box 69, Folder 611)
    - UTS: Special Events (Box 69, Folder 612)
  - Leadership in Voluntary Associations
    - Dayton Council on World Affairs/Great Decisions Discussions Group (Box 69, Folder 613)
  - Professional Associations
    - Academy of Evangelism: Correspondence, Papers, Publications (Box 69, Folder 615)
    - African Studies Association (ASA): Papers, 1970-1978 (Box 69, Folder 616)
    - American Society of Missiology: Annual Meetings (Box 69, Folder 617)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Finance (Box 69, Folder 618)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Manual for Sub-editors (Box 69, Folder 619)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Proposal; Reports (Box 69, Folder 620)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Selected Annotated Bibliography (Box 69, Folder 621)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Project Specifications (Box 69, Folder 622)
    - ASM: Bibliography Project: Sub-editors (Box 69, Folder 623)
    - ASM: Board of Publications (Box 69, Folder 624)
    - ASM: Book Editor: Book Publishers (Box 69, Folder 625)
    - ASM: Book Editor: Papers (Box 69, Folder 626)
    - ASM: Book Editor: Reports (Box 70, Folder 627)
    - ASM: Book Editor: Reviewers (Box 70, Folder 628)
    - Association for Case Teaching: Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 629)
    - Association of the Professors of Mission (APM): Annual Meetings (Box 70, Folder 632)
    - APM: Course Syllabi (Box 70, Folder 633)